hi everyone welcome to modules in JDK 9
大家好，欢迎使用JDK 9中的模块
my name is Alex Buckley and I write the
我叫亚历克斯·巴克利（Alex Buckley），
specification of the Java language and
Java语言规范和
the java virtual machine i've worked on
我工作过的Java虚拟机
the java platform since 2006 so i've
自2006年以来的Java平台，所以我
seen the full life cycles of JDK 7 8 &amp; 9
看到了JDK 7 8和9的整个生命周期
I worked on project coin and invoke
我研究了项目硬币并调用
dynamic in JDK 7 on lambdas and type
在Lambda和类型上的JDK 7中是动态的
annotations in JDK 8 and on the modules
JDK 8和模块中的注释
in JDK 9 that we'll be talking about
在JDK 9中，我们将要讨论
today first we'll talk about what
今天首先我们将讨论什么
modules are and how they improve the
模块以及它们如何改进
developer experience second we'll talk
开发人员体验第二，我们再谈
about how the JDK has been turned into
关于如何将JDK变成
modules and third we'll talk about some
模块，第三个我们将讨论一些
of the things you need to know about
您需要了解的事情
migrating to JDK 9 one of the core
迁移到JDK 9的核心之一
features of any programming language is
任何编程语言的特征是
the ability to reuse code so the large
重用代码的能力如此之大
programs can be built from small
程序可以从小构建
programs in Java the basic unit of reuse
Java中的程序是重用的基本单位
is traditionally the class Java has
传统上是Java拥有的类
wonderful mechanisms for promoting reuse
促进重用的绝佳机制
of a class such as inheritance for
类的继承
reusing behavior and interfaces for
重用行为和接口
reusing abstractions
重用抽象
however when your Java program gets to
但是，当您的Java程序进入
be 5 10 20 packages in 2 4 8 jar files
将5 10 20包放在2 4 8个jar文件中
it becomes difficult to visualize how
很难想象如何
all those classes and interfaces
所有这些类和接口
interact which means it's hard to
互动，这意味着很难
control who is reusing what just imagine
控制谁在重用只是想像的东西
how difficult it is to control reuse
控制重用有多困难
within a really large code base like the
在非常大的代码库（例如
217 official packages shown here from
此处显示217个官方包装
JDK 8 the only way to share code between
JDK 8之间共享代码的唯一方法
packages is with the public modifier but
包带有public修饰符，但是
then the code is shared with everyone a
然后将代码与所有人共享
package is a great way to organize
打包是一种很好的组织方式
classes but most people wish there was a
课，但大多数人希望有一个
way to organize packages to modules let
将软件包组织到模块的方法
you do that a module is a set of
你认为一个模块是一组
packages designed for reuse this is a
专为重复使用而设计的软件包
long-overdue building block in the java
Java中的过期过期构建基块
language
语言
in effect modules recalled to the
实际上召回给
structure of your program so that the
程序的结构，以便
parts you want to be reused can be
您想重复使用的零件可以是
reused
重用
while the parts you don't want to be
而你不想成为的部分
reused can't be reused a program built
重用不能重用构建的程序
of modules will be more reliable than a
的模块将比
program built from a loose set of
从一组松散的程序中构建的程序
packages in jar files that can access
可以访问的jar文件中的软件包
each other freely and that exposed to
彼此自由地接触
many api's to the outside world here's a
通往外界的许多API
module that everyone will soon be
每个人都将成为的模块
familiar with Java base it's the
熟悉Java基础的
foundation of every Java program like
每个Java程序的基础，例如
java.lang object is the root of every
java.lang对象是每个对象的根
class in blue are the packages of Java
蓝色的类是Java的软件包
base intended for use by code outside
旨在供外部代码使用的库
the module these are its exported
这些是其导出的模块
packages in red other packages internal
红色包装其他内部包装
to Java base they can be used by code
到Java基础，它们可以被代码使用
inside the module but not by code
在模块内部，但不是通过代码
outside the module these are its
在模块之外，这些是
concealed packages a module is declared
隐藏包声明了一个模块
in a new kind of file called module info
在一种称为模块信息的新文件中
Java it gives the name of the module and
Java，它给出了模块的名称，
its exported packages by exporting the
通过导出
java.lang package it means that the
java.lang包意味着
public classes of java.lang are
java.lang的公共类是
accessible from outside java base a
可从外部java base访问
package that is not explicitly exported
没有明确导出的包
such as calm sun crypto provider is
例如平静的太阳加密货币提供商是
concealed it's public classes are not
隐藏它的公共课不是
accessible outside java base this is the
在Java基础之外可以访问的是
first feature of modules in jdk 9 strong
JDK 9 Strong中模块的第一个功能
encapsulation a module isn't just a set
封装模块不仅仅是一组
of packages it's a set of exported
包，它是一组导出的
packages and concealed packages
包装和隐藏包装
this means that access control is more
这意味着访问控制更多
powerful in jdk 9 than in jdk 8 in
在jdk 9中比在jdk 8中强大
jeddah q9 you can arrange for public
吉达q9可以安排公共活动
classes to be accessible to everyone or
每个人都可以访问的课程，或者
accessible only to other classes in the
仅可用于
same module or accessible to classes in
同一模块或中的类可访问
the same module and a limb
相同的模块和肢体
set of friend modules so if you're
一组朋友模块，如果您
looking at public on a class declaration
在班级声明上看公众
it no longer means that everyone can
它不再意味着每个人都可以
access the class access depends on
访问类访问取决于
whether the class's module exports the
该类的模块是否导出
classes package when you write your own
编写自己的类包时
module you specify the modules it
您指定模块的模块
depends on this is the second feature of
取决于这是第二个特征
modules in JDK nine reliable dependences
JDK中的模块九个可靠依赖项
a module isn't just a set of packages
一个模块不仅仅是一组软件包
it's the set of packages that reuse the
这是重复使用
packages exported by other modules here
其他模块在此处导出的软件包
we have a hello world module that
我们有一个hello world模块，
exports a package of its own and depends
出口自己的包裹并依赖
on Java base with the requires keyword
在Java上使用require关键字
this means the code in the HelloWorld
这意味着HelloWorld中的代码
module can import any of the packages
模块可以导入任何软件包
exported by Java base but there is no
由Java库导出，但没有
way for code in the HelloWorld module to
HelloWorld模块中的代码的方式
import any of the packages concealed by
导入由...隐藏的任何软件包
Java base there are quite a few benefits
Java基础有很多好处
to putting code in modules for a starts
开始将代码放入模块中
the HelloWorld module can be run with a
HelloWorld模块可以与
simple Java command that points to a
指向一个简单的Java命令
directory of modules the minus P and the
负P和
module to be run the minus M you don't
要运行的模块减去您没有的M
need to set the class path the modules
需要设置模块的类路径
themselves say what they depend on JDK 9
自己说他们依赖JDK 9
checks the dependencies both when you
在您检查两者的依赖项时
compile and when you run it checks that
编译并在运行时检查
every module that is required is
所需的每个模块都是
available that's a big improvement over
可用，这是对
the class path where you don't discover
您找不到的课程路径
missing jars until later it checks that
缺少罐子，直到以后它检查
modules don't require each other in a
模块之间不需要彼此
cycle cycles lead to code that is hard
循环导致代码很难
to understand and maintain finally it
最终了解并维护它
checks that a package is exported from
检查软件包是否从中导出
exactly one other module this means
恰好是另一个模块，这意味着
there are no split packages split
没有拆分包拆分
packages are the mess you get on the
包是你上的烂摊子
class path when two jars contain the
两个罐子包含的类路径
same package and you load some classes
同一包，您加载了一些类
from one jar and other classes from the
来自一个罐子，来自其他罐子
other jar avoiding split packages is
另一个避免拆分包装的罐子是
also a win for performance because JDK 9
也是性能方面的胜利，因为JDK 9
knows exactly where each package
确切知道每个包裹在哪里
which is much better than repeatedly
比重复好很多
scanning every jar on the classpath
扫描类路径上的每个jar
looking for a needed class by the way
顺便找一个需要的课程
modules are not mandatory you can keep
模块不是强制性的，您可以保留
putting jars on the classpath and jdk 9
将罐子放在classpath和jdk 9上
supports a gradual migration to modules
支持逐步迁移到模块
so that you can choose the trade-off of
这样您可以选择权衡
how much work you're willing to do to
你愿意做多少工作
modularize versus the benefits of
模块化与好处
modules let's turn our attention to the
模块让我们将注意力转向
JDK 20 years ago the Java platform was
JDK 20年前，Java平台是
small just a few hundred classes and the
小的只有几百堂课，
organization of the JDK wasn't a problem
JDK的组织不是问题
but every year the platform grew bigger
但是平台每年都变大
and now it's tens of thousands of
现在有成千上万
classes the JDK is huge and worse its
JDK是巨大的，更糟糕​​的是
monolithic in reality the Java platform
实际上是Java平台的整体式
is not one thing it's more like 25
不是一回事，更像是25
separate frameworks including the swing
单独的框架，包括秋千
UI framework a crypto framework a
UI框架加密框架
scripting framework multiple XML
脚本框架多个XML
processing frameworks and so on there's
处理框架等等
no reason these separate frameworks have
这些单独的框架没有理由
to be tightly coupled in one download in
在一个下载中紧密耦合
fact it's an impediment in developing
事实上这是发展的障碍
the JDK the overly tight coupling raises
JDK过紧的联轴器引起
development and testing costs which
开发和测试费用
turns into slower platform evolution
变成平台发展缓慢
plus the larger the surface of your
再加上您的表面较大
platform the more difficult it is to
平台越难
secure and it's an impediment to a lot
安全，这是很多障碍
of users both those who want to run
的用户都想要运行
their applications on smaller devices
它们在较小设备上的应用
and those who want to run more instances
以及那些想运行更多实例的人
of their of their application on large
在大型应用程序中的应用
systems even if you only wanted a part
系统，即使您只想要一部分
of the JDK you've had to take all of it
JDK，您必须全部使用
that all changes in JDK 9 we've taken
我们已经采取了JDK 9中的所有更改
the monolithic JDK and broken it up into
整体式JDK并将其分解为
a few dozen modules some of these are
几十个模块，其中一些是
part of the Java SE specification some
Java SE规范的一部分
are just part of the JDK implementation
只是JDK实现的一部分
here's a graph of the Java SE modules at
这是Java SE模块的图形，位于
the bottom there's Java base which
底部有Java基础
everything depends on and which depends
一切都取决于，取决于
on nothing itself we've broken out the
在没有任何事情上，我们已经打破了
various frameworks into their own
将各种框架整合到自己的框架中
modules instrumentation logging XML
模块仪表记录XML
scripting desktop which you can require
您可能需要的脚本桌面
or not require as you'll need to dictate
或不需要，因为您需要决定
there's a Java SE module which has no
有一个Java SE模块没有
actual code in it but just has
实际的代码，但只有
dependences so you can say requires java
依赖关系，所以您可以说需要Java
SE and be guaranteed to have all these
SE，并保证拥有所有这些
modules available it's worth mentioning
可用模块值得一提
that merely finding these module
仅仅找到这些模块
boundaries which might be obvious in
边界可能在
hindsight was a tremendous engineering
后见之明是一项巨大的工程
effort you'll find in your own code that
您在自己的代码中会发现
decoupling a monolith is much harder
解耦整体要困难得多
than building a loosely coupled system
比建立一个松散耦合的系统
from the beginning
从一开始就
the good news going forward is that the
未来的好消息是
discipline imposed by modules will
模块施加的纪律将
prevent all of us from accidentally
防止我们所有人意外
recreating a monolith I'd like to
重建我想要的整体
quickly review the expectations of
快速查看以下人员的期望
compatibility from JDK 9 first up there
首先是JDK 9的兼容性
are various technologies from Java EE
Java EE的各种技术
that ship in the JDK as well as in app
在JDK和应用程序中都附带
servers the list of Java EE modules in
服务器中的Java EE模块列表
JDK 9 includes Cober Jack's B jax-ws and
JDK 9包括Cober Jack的B jax-ws和
common annotations these modules are
这些模块的通用注释是
deprecated in JDK 9 and will be removed
JDK 9中已弃用，将其删除
in a future release because of this they
因此，在将来的版本中
are disabled by default in JDK 9 if
如果在JDK 9中默认禁用
you're running code on the classpath you
您正在您的类路径上运行代码
may need to use the add modules command
可能需要使用添加模块命令
line flag to enable the Java EE modules
行标记以启用Java EE模块
second a lot of tools and libraries try
其次很多工具和库尝试
to access parts of the JDK that are
访问JDK的以下部分
meant for internal use only
仅供内部使用
unfortunately it'll take a while for
不幸的是，这需要一段时间
tool and library developers to move away
工具和库开发人员转移
from this practice so JDK 9 temporarily
从这种做法，所以JDK 9暂时
allows access to JDK internals but
允许访问JDK内部，但
prints a warning when it happens there's
发生警告时会显示警告
a command line flag to avoid these
命令行标志以避免这些
warnings so please check with tool and
警告，因此请使用工具和
library developers about how to deploy
库开发人员有关如何部署的信息
on JDK 9 finally there are miscellaneous
最后在JDK 9上还有其他
changes in JDK 9 that are unrelated to
JDK 9中与以下内容无关的更改
modules but might affect code that ran
模块，但可能会影响运行的代码
on JDK 8 notably code that assumes the
在JDK 8上，特别是假设
Java version stream begins with one dot
Java版本流以一个点开头
or assumes that the JDK lives in a file
或假设JDK位于文件中
called RT jar will fail on JDK 9 again
调用RT jar将再次在JDK 9上失败
please
请
check with tool and library developers
与工具和库开发人员核对
about which versions are needed to run
关于需要运行哪些版本
on JDK 9 to conclude JDK 9 is important
在JDK 9上得出结论，JDK 9很重要
because it enables modular development
因为它支持模块化开发
all the way down the java language and
一直到Java语言
the java virtual machine understand
Java虚拟机了解
modules very deeply so that the
模块非常深入，因此
applications you write and the libraries
您编写的应用程序和库
you consume and even the jdk itself can
你消耗，甚至jdk本身可以
all be developed and tested and packaged
全部经过开发，测试和打包
and deployed as modules with clear api's
并部署为带有清晰API的模块
and well protected internals making
并保护好内部零件
everyone play by the same modular rules
每个人都遵循相同的模块化规则
has great benefits for reliability
对可靠性有很大好处
maintainability and security though it
可维护性和安全性
may take some time for popular tools and
流行的工具可能需要一些时间，
libraries to catch up you can download
图书馆赶上你可以下载
JDK 9 now and follow what's happening
现在使用JDK 9并关注正在发生的事情
with JDK development at open JDK also
在开放的JDK上进行JDK开发
follow us on Twitter at open JDK and
在开放的JDK上在Twitter上关注我们，并
hashtag Java 9 and with that thank you
Java 9标签，谢谢
very much
非常